Now that you have the focal flowers in, the next thing we need to do is to add some accent flowers along with this.
One of the things that's the best to do and to help keep the cost down on doing flower arrangements in silk is you buy a bush.
Which is consistent of flowers together coming down to one stem and then you can cut them apart.
So what you try to do is you cut your flowers to a reasonable length that you think will work in the bridal bouquet.
And you can start placing them in supporting the look of your focal flowers.
And the other positive thing about doing silk flowers is that you can just bend and arrange them any which way you like.
Fresh flowers it's basically God's made them and you've just got to work with what He's given you to do it.
You need to make sure that you're keeping an eye on the fact that this is going to be rounded or seen also from the side.
So we need to make sure that the side is covered as well.
But this is usually what you use with the smaller flowers and your greeneries.
But you need to put some color in there as well so it looks good from a distance.
Okay and the other thing is is this is a typical different flower.
We're going to start adding texture to it and that will be another part of the filler flowers that we add.
So right now what we're doing is putting in filler to support the main rose flowers.
And that's the end of this step.